Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Come on.
تعال.
This glass
هذا الزجاج
is to celebrate Mr. Wen Pei'an's
وذلك للاحتفال بـ
modeling career
مهنة عرض الأزياء
debut
أول مرة
being a complete success.
تحقيق نجاح كامل.
Bottoms up.
إلى أسفل.
This second glass
هذا الكأس الثاني
celebrates the two of us
نحتفل نحن الاثنين
for today's performance
لأداء اليوم
being a total victory.
تحقيق نصر كامل.
At the time, I thought
في ذلك الوقت، كنت أعتقد
with our acting skills,
بفضل مهاراتنا التمثيلية،
we could've starred in *Lurk*.
كان بإمكاننا أن نكون أبطال فيلم *Lurk*.
You're way too slow.
أنت بطيء للغاية.
This third glass...
هذا الكأس الثالث...
This is liquor,
هذا مشروب كحولي،
not water.
ليس ماءً.
Of course I know it's liquor.
بالطبع أعرف أنه مشروب كحولي.
Me,
أنا،
I have a high tolerance.
لدي قدرة عالية على التحمل.
If you can't handle it,
إذا لم تستطع التعامل مع الأمر،
just drink less.
قلل من شرب الكحول.
I can tell you can't handle it.
أستطيع أن أقول إنك لا تستطيع التعامل مع الأمر.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I do have a boyfriend.
نعم، لديّ حبيب.
Really?
حقًا؟
How come you've never mentioned him?
لماذا لم تذكره أبداً؟
Cash.
نقدي.
Cash is my boyfriend.
كاش هو حبيبي.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I'm really, really envious of you.
أنا أغبطك بشدة.
I envy that you have
أغبطك على امتلاكك
parents who love you so much.
والداكِ اللذان يحبانكِ كثيراً.
Your parents don't love you?
ألا يحبك والداك؟
Probably not.
ربما لا.
Because
لأن
I've never even seen them.
لم أرهم قط.
To be precise,
على وجه الدقة،
it's that
هذا هو
the moment I was born,
لحظة ولادتي،
they abandoned me.
لقد تخلوا عني.
I grew up in an orphanage.
نشأت في دار للأيتام.
When I was little,
عندما كنت صغيراً،
I'd see those kids
كنت أرى هؤلاء الأطفال
being taken out by their parents,
يصطحبهم آباؤهم في نزهة،
going out to play.
الخروج للعب.
They got tasty food
لقد حصلوا على طعام لذيذ
and wore pretty clothes.
وارتدت ملابس جميلة.
You have no idea how much I envied them.
ليس لديك أدنى فكرة عن مدى حسدي لهم.
So,
لذا،
when I was seven years old,
عندما كنت في السابعة من عمري،
I thought I did
ظننت أنني فعلت ذلك
something incredibly brave.
شيء شجاع للغاية.
I ran away from the orphanage.
هربت من دار الأيتام.
I wanted to go out
أردت الخروج
and find my
واعثر على لي
mom and dad.
أمي وأبي.
Hey, kid.
يا فتى.
Why are you alone?
لماذا أنت وحيد؟
Mister,
سيدي،
could you buy me a bun?
هل يمكنك أن تشتري لي كعكة؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
I'll treat you.
سأتكفل بدفع الحساب.
Why are you here by yourself?
لماذا أنت هنا بمفردك؟
My parents are coming to pick me up soon.
سيأتي والداي لأخذي قريباً.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
I ran away from home on purpose.
هربت من المنزل عن قصد.
Be gone for two hours,
سأغيب لمدة ساعتين،
show my parents who's boss.
أري والديّ من هو الرئيس.
You should go home.
يجب أن تعود إلى المنزل.
You'll miss them.
ستفتقدهم.
I won't miss them at all.
لن أفتقدهم على الإطلاق.
Will you miss yours?
هل ستفتقدها؟
It's about time.
لقد حان الوقت.
I should head home.
يجب أن أعود إلى المنزل.
You should go home early too.
يجب عليك العودة إلى المنزل مبكراً أيضاً.
Of course, the result was obvious.
وبالطبع، كانت النتيجة واضحة.
I didn't find them.
لم أجدهم.
Because I had no idea
لأنني لم أكن أعرف
what they even looked like.
حتى شكلهم.
Don't look at me with such pity.
لا تنظر إليّ بهذه النظرة الشفقة.
Personally, I feel
شخصياً، أشعر
my childhood
طفولتي
was actually quite happy.
كنت سعيدًا جدًا في الواقع.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
I'm not bragging,
أنا لا أتباهى،
but I'm someone
لكنني شخص ما
who's very smart.
وهو ذكي جداً.
No matter what I learn,
مهما تعلمت،
as long as
طالما
I see it three times,
أراه ثلاث مرات،
I can master it.
أستطيع إتقانها.
Do you believe me?
هل تصدقني؟
I believe you.
واعتقد انكم.
You don't believe me?
ألا تصدقني؟
In today's society,
في مجتمع اليوم،
educational background is highly valued.
الخلفية التعليمية تحظى بتقدير كبير.
For someone like me,
بالنسبة لشخص مثلي،
with a low level of education,
بمستوى تعليمي منخفض،
it's really hard
الأمر صعب حقاً
to get by in this world.
للعيش في هذا العالم.
Can you understand?
هل تفهم؟
I can understand.
أتفهم ذلك.
If you were to say
لو قلت
you can't understand,
لا يمكنك أن تفهم،
but even if you don't,
ولكن حتى لو لم تفعل ذلك،
that's okay too.
لا بأس بذلك أيضاً.
But honestly,
لكن بصراحة،
I'm very grateful
أنا ممتن جداً
that my current company
تلك شركتي الحالية
doesn't care about my education.
لا يهتم بتعليمي.
But recently,
لكن مؤخراً،
our company
شركتنا
got a new bastard in charge.
تولى شخص جديد وضيع المسؤولية.
That
الذي - التي
bas-
تحت-
tard.
متأخر.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
this bastard,
هذا الوغد،
as soon as he took over,
بمجرد أن تولى منصبه،
he destroyed
لقد دمر
all the proposals
جميع المقترحات
I worked so hard on.
لقد بذلت جهداً كبيراً في ذلك.
What the hell does he know?
ما الذي يعرفه بحق الجحيم؟
Such a great company...
شركة رائعة حقاً...
I'm really worried
أنا قلق للغاية
that as soon as he took over,
أنه بمجرد توليه المنصب،
he'd ruin this company.
سيدمر هذه الشركة.
Have you ever considered
هل فكرت يومًا في
that this situation
أن هذا الوضع
might be viewed differently by everyone?
قد ينظر إليها الجميع بشكل مختلف؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Let me ask you,
دعني أسألك،
what is the
ما هو
fundamental rule
القاعدة الأساسية
for a boyfriend?
كحبيب؟
It's that
هذا هو
whoever the girlfriend
أياً كانت الصديقة
curses at,
يسب،
the boyfriend must curse at too.
يجب على الحبيب أن يشتم أيضاً.
Come on, come on, come on.
هيا، هيا، هيا.
Curse with me.
لعن معي.
My boss
رئيسي
is a
هو
stupid little bastard.
هذا الوغد الصغير الغبي.
Your boss
رئيسك
is a stupid little bastard.
إنه وغد صغير غبي.
That's not good enough.
هذا ليس جيداً بما فيه الكفاية.
You have to be louder.
يجب أن تكون أكثر صخباً.
Come on.
تعال.
With me,
معي،
shout it out loud!
اصرخ بها بصوت عالٍ!
MY BOSS
رئيسي
IS A
هو
STUPID
غبي
LITTLE BASTARD!
يا ابن العاهرة الصغير!
YOUR BOSS
رئيسك
IS A
هو
STUPID
غبي
LITTLE BASTARD!
يا ابن العاهرة الصغير!
He is a stupid little bastard!
إنه وغد صغير غبي!
Xin Tong!
شين تونغ!
Darn it, Wen Pei'an!
اللعنة عليك يا وين بي آن!
You're a beast!
أنت وحش!
Wen Pei'an!
ون بيان!
Tell me,
أخبرني،
what did you do
ماذا فعلت؟
to me last night?
ماذا قلت لي الليلة الماضية؟
I didn't do anything.
لم أفعل شيئاً.
I demand
أطالب
to see the rooftop surveillance from last night.
لمشاهدة تسجيلات كاميرات المراقبة على سطح المبنى من الليلة الماضية.
No.
لا.
You have no right to see it.
ليس لك الحق في رؤيته.
Fine.
بخير.
If you won't show me,
إذا لم تُظهر لي،
you must have a guilty conscience.
لا بد أن لديك ضميراً مذنباً.
I could choose to call the police.
كان بإمكاني اختيار الاتصال بالشرطة.
I can use the power of the law
يمكنني استخدام قوة القانون
to punish you.
لمعاقبتك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
معذرة، معذرة، معذرة.
I really didn't mean to.
لم أقصد ذلك حقاً.
It's okay, it's okay.
لا بأس، لا بأس.
Let me wash your clothes.
دعني أغسل ملابسك.
I must wash them for you.
يجب أن أغسلها لك.
I have to take responsibility.
يجب أن أتحمل المسؤولية.
You...
أنت...
Give me a chance.
أعطني فرصة.
I'll wash them clean for you.
سأغسلها لك حتى تصبح نظيفة.
I'll definitely wash them clean.
سأغسلها بالتأكيد.
Give them here!
أعطهم هنا!
You...
أنت...
wait here for me.
انتظرني هنا.
Don't worry, I'll definitely wash them clean.
لا تقلق، سأغسلها بالتأكيد.
Go over there and wait.
اذهب إلى هناك وانتظر.
It'll be quick.
سيكون الأمر سريعاً.
Wait here for me.
انتظرني هنا.
Xin Tong!
شين تونغ!
I'll be quick!
سأكون سريعاً!
Wait for me!
الانتظار لي!
Xin Tong, give my clothes back!
شين تونغ، أعد لي ملابسي!
Xin Tong!
شين تونغ!
Right.
يمين.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Is that enough?
هل هذا يكفي؟
I'm so sorry.
أنا آسف جدا.
I'm truly sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
I'm not usually like this when I drink.
أنا لستُ عادةً هكذا عندما أشرب.
After I wash these clothes clean,
بعد أن أغسل هذه الملابس جيداً،
I'll return them to you.
سأعيدها إليك.
I advise you
أنصحك
to quit drinking from now on.
أن أتوقف عن شرب الكحول من الآن فصاعداً.
I swear,
أقسم،
I won't drink anymore.
لن أشرب الكحول بعد الآن.
That outfit you're wearing
هذا الزي الذي ترتديه
is very stylish.
أنيق للغاية.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
This morning, our marketing department
هذا الصباح، قسم التسويق لدينا
has a meeting with President Galileo.
يعقد اجتماعاً مع الرئيس غاليليو.
Darn it, I forgot!
يا إلهي، لقد نسيت!
I'm on my way right now!
أنا في طريقي الآن!
I know, I know.
أعرف، أعرف.
Remember to take your medicine.
تذكر أن تأخذ دوائك.
Be right there.
سأكون هناك حالا.
Do you need a ride?
هل تحتاج إلى توصيلة؟
Is that okay?
هل هذا مناسب؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Four Seas Tower.
برج البحار الأربعة.